It's project time again. So, what I'm
going to have you do is I'm going to
have you build this trivia app here. Um,
basically what you're going to do is
you're going to fetch the questions from
the API, store the questions in local
storage, and then, um, display a
question on the screen out of local
storage. The correct answer you're going
to store in session storage. Um, and
then you're going to display the
questions using jQuery and handle all of
the interaction with the user using
jQuery. When they're correct, I want you
to automatically load the next question.
Once they've answered all of the
questions, I want you to go back to the
API and grab some new questions.
Um, to show you what the user interface
looks like, this is the user interface.
Um, you're going to replace this
placeholder text with the trivia
question, and then they're going to
answer by either clicking true or false
based on that trivia question. And then
you'll just give them the feedback
accordingly.